[Music]
All right. So, today we're going to be
going through some prompt writing with
Google Flow. And I prepared a little PDF
to go over here with you guys. Let me
see if I can open it.
So, we're going to have a quick workshop
on how to write prompts. So, we're going
to go to the prompting part of the PDF
right there. Prompt formula template,
breaking down each element, beginner
mistakes to avoid, and testing prompts.
This PDF is free and available to you
guys. Um I'll tell you how to get it in
a second. Okay, tell you how to get it
in a second. Let's go ahead and um
start talking about what what am I
talking about prompts? Where where are
you going to enter those prompts? So, a
lot of people think it's like chat GPT
or something. It's not. Prompts are
going to be entered into Google Flow,
which is the application that I've been
teaching here for the past two months.
Google Flow is a membership of Google AI
Pro, which is accessible through this
plan right here, Google AI Pro. And just
to set the ground, it's $20 a month. You
can get it for free for the first month.
So, just to begin, I want to start with
that, letting you guys know it's this is
what I'm using. If somebody's asking in
the chat, please let them know that it's
Google Flow and it's a subscription of
Google AI Pro. $20 a month. You can make
140 videos a month with this. So, let me
go ahead and move. Let's see. Let me
move this out of my way here so I can
get started with
Google Flow. So, this is Flow. I'm in
Google Flow right now. And I've been
creating videos left and right with
this. There's a bunch of videos in my
account. Let's take a look at some of
the stuff that you can make. And then
we're going to talk about those prompts
and how it works out in the back uh in
uh in the background here. So it all
starts with just the text. Okay. So for
example, this one
let's see if you can get to a
So these were started with the image. So
I created the image first. Let me go
back to the beginning actually. Hold on
here. So I created this image on chat
GPT
with the prompt. Obviously I just wrote
something like you know huge whale under
a boat under a small boat in the deep
ocean. And then once I uploaded that
image using the frames to video here,
we're going to go ahead and write your
your action that you want to happen. So
the image was made into a video like
this.
Hold on, let me lower the volume on this
real quick.
So the volume, what would the volume of
this be? Hold on, guys.
I think the volume of that would be
right here. I got a new mixer. So, I got
to make sure my volumes are adjusted
right.
Got the line out.
Got my microphone.
Can you guys hear this whale um video?
Let me know by saying yes in the chat.
Can you hear just like a noise in the
back?
Yes. Okay, cool.
So that is the prompt that we generated
by just saying overhead orbit whale
breaches partially behind the boat water
spraying the vessel dwarfed by its
immense size. So that's all I wrote and
that animated that image that I told you
about. This is an image that I started
with.
So that's what happens. It breached the
boat. See the boats on top of it. You
can hear you can hear the splashing. So
I did several of them trying to get
trying to get good visuals. So that's
what the prompting is. Now this is a
prompt with a
text I mean with an image with the
image. It's a it's a image to video. Now
if you want to create a prompt
completely from scratch from like a
text. Let's watch this one here.
Okay. So, look, this is a this is the
baby trend I jumped on to try to teach
you guys how to do this, but it's
difficult to make these little baby talk
on these on these uh on this app.
Sometimes they don't let you do it. So,
here, a newborn. This is a complete text
prompt. A newborn baby with his face
painted like the Joker staring into a
mirror over the shoulder shot, dark
scene, moody light. Um, he blankly
stares making uh making Joker like mouth
movements. So, I wanted to see if it
would kind of do his mannerisms.
So, you see there's no dialogue on this
one,
but over here we have dialogue.
A newborn baby with his face painted
like the Joker. He's sitting in his
hospital bed, moody light, moody
lighting, uh, cinematic environment. He
says, "Where is the doctor? I want to
ask him why he's so serious." So, here,
baby Joker says this.
Oh yeah, that's the that's the manic
laugh right here at the end. So that
happened for us.
So let's break down what a prompt how
it's assembled because I know a lot of
people are still having issues with
knowing how to write them and how to get
just the right mix how to get the right
mix of um of information.
they're not telling it what to do exact
like they're not they're not being clear
with what you know what they want the
video to do and this is how you're going
to be clear about it okay so this is the
part of this PDF that we're going to
talk about this is available in my uh
bio link is in bio for that it's the
first link it says how to create V3
videos and then once you get in that
page it's going to have an option for
you to download a free PDF or for you to
join a paid course so this is how you
get this PDF you go ahead and download
the free PDF
So, this is this is what the PDF covers.
Okay, we have an introduction. Some
people don't have no idea what V3 is.
Let me go ahead and show you the PDF
screen.
There you go. So, some people don't know
what V3 is, so I explained it briefly on
there. Who is this guide for for
beginners? So, if you're already
somebody that's already making these
videos and you just need some help some
help with prompts, just go ahead to the
prompting part of the PDF. So, it's very
clear. I I hope it's useful to you guys.
So, uh so let's just jump into the
prompting part. I'm going to break down
how a prompt works for V3 at least.
So, it's chapter 2. So, chapter 2 is
prompted.
Chapter 2 is prompted. So, I'm going to
skip over the the little fluff stuff,
the reading. Let's go back to Let's go
directly to this. how a texttovideo
prompt works. So, first of all, in a
text to video prompt, you're going to
need a character. In that case, was the
one that I just showed you, right? Was a
newborn baby. We need the camera,
meaning the camera angle, like the
framing, for example, wide shot, a
medium shot. Okay. You need a setting.
What's the setting like? Hospital bed is
the setting, for example. Remember how I
wrote the hospital? And then the
lighting. Moody lighting. Remember I
those the scene with the mirror? I said
moody. Uh, or you can say high key.
Highkey means like daytime. Low key
means dark.
Wait, where did you find this? I made
this this guide. I made it. It's in my
uh it's free for you to download. Just
go to the link in bio
and you can download it. But hopefully
you stay here for now. Don't don't leave
yet because if you leave then you might
not get back in. You might forget it. So
don't jump the trigger and go there yet.
You can get this. It's not going to go
anywhere. I made this guide. So, uh,
next we have action and dialogue. So,
action meaning, you know, uh, for
example, Bigfoot runs and dialogue is he
says, "I'm not leaving yet, brother."
All right, cool. So, here's I'm going to
do a a full example of what I mean by by
these by these components right here.
Let me guys, let me give me one second.
Let make sure my uh my audio is good
because I can't tell. I get nervous
about the audio. Sometimes people don't
tell me and I look at the recording and
the audio doesn't work right. So, let me
get let me double check here. I'm I'm
live in multiple places. So, I got to
check all the places first.
So, I'm sure you can start you can start
reading behind me what it says right
there. So, when I get to it, you know
what I'm talking about.
>> All right. I think it sounds good. Let
me just mute my uh
All right. Sorry, guys. I'm just working
on that music. It was a little too loud.
So, here we go. We got example. Bigfoot
with the selfie camera angle. So, that's
the character. Okay. That's the
character and the camera angle. Bigfoot
with the selfie camera angle. Character
camera angle. Done. What's the setting?
Oh, the this the the camera still goes
here. Look. Camera angle. Shot from
extended arm perspective vlog style. So,
that's all character and camera. Okay.
Uh, setting. There are two trees
surrounding the scene. So, that's the
setting. Behind him, there is a big
forest fire. Still setting. Lighting.
What's the lighting like?
DJI is an AI. Yeah, sometimes I wish I
was AI. Do whatever I want. So, here we
go. Um,
the There are trees towering.
There are towering trees surrounding the
scene. Behind them there is a big forest
fire. So that's the setting. So the
lighting, the atmosphere is foggy and
cinematic. It's golden hour near sunset.
So this is the lighting, guys. That's
the when I say lighting, that's the
lighting. I don't know why this keeps
happening, guys. The the
setting button keeps coming up. Not
clicking anything different.
Hide for this session. All right, I'm
not going to click anything. So that's
the that's the lighting sunset. What's
the action in the dialogue? Here's the
action. He runs away from the forest
fire as fast as he can and says that's
the dialogue. That's what he says. Man,
I've outdone myself now. I guess I
didn't think that through. So, that is
how you write a full prompt. That's
going to be something that you can copy
and paste and then change it however you
want in your own in your own words. So,
this is the first piece of it.
Character. Okay. So, the character
description, describe the character in
details. For example, Bigfoot wearing a
denim jacket and a torn red feno shirt
and muddy cargo pants. So, you're going
to tell you're going to tell V2 V3
exactly how your character looks. If you
just say Bigfoot, that's fine. It's
going to give you Bigfoot. But, if you
want it to be exactly dressed the way
you want it, that's the time that you're
going to tell it how you want it to
dress. So, you can also make something
that's consistent, like a consistent
character. You might want to write
something like
uh with the black shirt that says DJI in
white font. You can just use that every
time so your character can be
consistent.
So now the next part is the camera
or the camera movement, right? So that's
the next component. So the camera
movement
or the camera angle sounds something
like this. Selfie camera angle shot from
extended arm perspective vlog style. And
you can say the camera is shaky as if
being uh held by someone running. So all
those things are going to direct how
your video is going to come out.
So all those things are going to direct
how your video is going to come out. So
we have camera done. Let's move on to
the setting and the lighting. So the
setting details provide specific details
about an environment. Example, this is
an example from the full prompt before.
All right, let me stop and see what the
chat's saying here. Do you have a list
of camera angles corresponding with that
angle actually looks like? Yes, I do.
It's um
it's
it's behind my it's in my course. It's
not on this guide here.
I can revise the guide and add the
camera angles. Let me see if it's in
here. I put as much as I could in here
for a free value. I think the camera
angles might be something that I don't
have in here, but I'll tell you right
now. So, the camera angle, I have a a
cheat sheet.
Uh, let me see if I can d Let me show
you. Let me show on the screen right
here. Let me pull it up.
So, before I proceed, let me pull up the
camera angles and then maybe you can
take a screenshot. Okay,
it's in my course. So, that's going to
be something that um it's not on this
guide, but I'm going to pull up the
camera angle so you can see it.
So, it's not this one.
So, this this is this is part of all the
documentation that's in my course, but
that's not the one that I'm talking
about. The one that I want is
pull it up.
I have so many PDFs.
Shot composition guide.
All right. So, I'm going to pull up the
camera angles here in a second. Um, I
found it.
Got it. Shot composition guide. Here we
go. Whoa, that's big. Okay.
So, this is this is this is the framing.
Okay. All right, Logan. So, when we talk
about
when we talk about the camera angles,
this is it. So, we got a close-up,
medium closeup, medium shot, medium wide
shot, a wide shot, and extreme wide
shot.
And then on the bottom here, you can't
see it, but it says aerial drone shot.
So, those are those are the camera
angles. And then you also have the
selfie one. I I didn't have enough room
to put in here, but I just thought that
would be obvious. selfie camera angle
will be you know like like this
like that's a selfie camera angle right
there. So this is all the resources that
you get um inside of the course but this
is all this right here minus the photos
are in the free guide. So everything
that I just showed you here with this
the prompt example and the breakdown all
that it's here just a different format.
So so let's move on to um setting
detail. So provide specific detail about
the environment. Example, towering pine
trees surrounding the scene. A massive
uh forest fire rages casting on an
orange glow. The ground is covered in
dry leaves and scattered across uh
scattered rocks
that he tumbles over. So this is just
like an example of a video that I did. I
don't have the visual for you to see,
but this is just an example of what a a
setting description would look like for
you. So then lighting style.
So, Pam Pam's asking, "Please, what uh
what's the website where we can watch
the course?" I bought it already, but I
forgot the website. Okay, so you're
going to go to I'm going to type it for
you here in the chat. You're going to go
to wp.com
and then you can even do for/lo
if you want to go directly to the login.
Enter the email. I put that in the chat.
Enter the email that you signed up with
and then you're going to get a
verification code. that's that's going
to that's going to be like your password
for that. Every time you log in, it's
going to generate a verification code.
Uh because that platform doesn't have a
password. So once you go in there,
you're going to see it. If it's on the
computer, you're going to see it on the
left side of the screen, a blue icon
that says DJI on it. That's the course.
And if you have any issues, just DM me
here. I can help you with what email you
used. If you forgot, um I can help you
with that. If you forgot, just tell me
the name that you signed up with and
I'll find your name in the course and
I'll tell you what email cuz some people
use multiple emails. So, another another
place that you are going to be able to
find this is in my bio. So, if you go to
the bio, this is a free guide. It's a
free V3 guide for beginners. So, I made
this guide.
So, if you guys want to go ahead and
grab it for free, it's all in my bio.
And then if you want the course, that's
going to be the video steps of
everything that's or not everything, but
um this this guide covers about 80% of
what you need to know and then the the
course will cover 100% of what you need
to know in a video format. Okay.
So,
let me go back to the prompt guide here
because this is what we're going to be
discussing. Again, this is this is the
type of stuff that you can create with
the text prompt. And these are the shot
compositions that you can use when
describing your prompts. And the
elements of the prompts are
character,
camera setting. Oh, character, camera,
setting, lighting, action, and dialogue.
So all those all those are components of
your text prompt. So I finished reading
at lighting style. So
here's a lighting style example. The
atmosphere is foggy and cinematic. It's
golden hour near sunset.
um dramatic lighting from the low sun
and the intense glowing of fi of fire.
So this is this is what you get with
something like that prompt. You see?
So this is an example of what you get.
Now let's go back to talking about the
lighting, the the action and dialogue.
So describe the action in any spoken
word. So if your character is speaking,
just say it. I enjoy learning from you.
Thank you, man. I appreciate it. I need
some coffee. It's It's a Saturday night.
I worked a long shift today here at the
office.
Mainly finishing this PDF for you guys.
I wanted to get this out there because I
know people are struggling with writing
prompts. So, I made this extra resource
in addition to the course.
And sometimes, guys, it's not your
fault. Sometimes if your prompts aren't
coming out the way you want it, it's not
your fault. If you're following the
method and you're being specific and
you're tweaking it and it's still not
coming out right because the characters
are swapping words or they're not
looking at each other, it's not your
fault. It's just it's just AI. It's not
perfect yet. I I wasted so many prompts,
so many credits trying to do multiple
prompts until I get the right like I
showed you guys before. I showed you my
screen before how many times I try to
get the whale video and I know how to
write prompts like I I can write them in
my sleep. It's not the problem is not
me, it's just the AI.
So here, for example, for the action and
the dialogue, describe the action in any
spoken words. Example, he runs away from
the forest fire as fast as he can,
stumbling slightly on the root on the
route and looking back over his
shoulders in a panicked, wideeyed
expression.
He says, so now this is the action was
already described right here. Remember
action and dialogue. Now here's the
dialogue. He says, "Man, I've outrun
I've I've outrun uh I've Oh, this is a
different prompt." Okay, I was going to
say, "Man, I've outdone myself." Cuz I
write that all the time. Man, I've
outran park rangers. Uh but this is a
whole new level of uh catch me if you
can. So, this is another video that I
created. Unfortunately, I couldn't put
the video here in the PDF, but this is
just an example of um
of how you're going to write these
prompts. Okay. So, common mistakes that
people make when they're writing their
prompts. This is a common mistake. Okay.
Well, one first an obvious one is don't
get frustrated. If it's not coming out
right, just take a breath and try it
again. But the common mistakes is uh
being too vague. You know, they're
they're saying something like, "Yo, make
it exciting." It's not ch. It doesn't
like think for you. You have to tell it
what to do. You can't just say like make
it exciting. Make make your scene funny.
You can't do that because you need to
tell it how to make it funny. So that
won't work as well as saying add action
music to the background or you know
that specifically saying what kind of
theme you want. You know add action
music, add suspense music in the
background. If you want to do that you
can say something like that. Now you're
giving it too many instructions at once
that can that can cause it to just panic
and not give you a quality prompt a
quality output. I mean, so, uh, break
big tasks into smaller steps or mult or
even multiple prompts. So, if you're
trying to do something that's too big,
cut it up into multiple prompts. And if
it's carrying on too long, just combine
all those videos into one video. So, if
you want to make like a 10-second video,
for example, you might need you might
need and it's complicated, you might
need to do like five different clips.
So, but you're like, wait, each clip is
eight seconds. So, five of them is 40
seconds. how I want to make just a
10-second clip. Because it's so
complicated, you're going to break it
down into a bunch of clips just to get
specifically what you want to see out of
it. And then you're going to take it to
the editing app and then go ahead and
edit that for yourself.
Don't try to do all these cutscenes if
it's getting too crazy. It you won't get
quality results.
So, uh so break big tasks into smaller
or multiple prompts. Remember, you only
have 8 seconds. So, if you're trying to
do too much inside the 8 seconds, it's
going to get complicated.
Um, skipping modifier. So, modifiers are
are something like
uh like the lighting, the mood. So,
those are extra words that you can add
to make the video more unique. So, if
you want something specific, just say
it. For example, add music is too vague.
So, you want to say add fast, energetic
music is a lot better than just saying
add music. So, ignoring feedback. If VO3
doesn't get it perfect the first time,
that's okay. Read it again and then
adjust your prompt. Adjust it a little
bit. Don't get too far away from what
your prompt um initial prompt idea was.
Yeah, if your prompts are too much.
Maybe my prompts are too much. Yeah, I
think I asked you for a sample. So, if
you can send it to me. I didn't see it
yet, but if you did it already, great.
I'll take a look at it. Maybe your
prompts are just getting too too long or
complicated. Just break it down. Make it
more simple. If you're giving it too
much instruction, it's it's going to
it's going to panic and do something
completely different. So, it's all about
about experimenting and learning. So, we
have um some examples of when I say
modifiers. Here's where they are. Look,
we have style modifiers. So, add
cinematic or animated or retro or
modern. Um you can say things like that.
If you want an animated video, just say
it's animated. If you want a cinematic,
just say cinematic. Those are specific
words that are going to help you to get
the visuals that you want. Now, I'm just
talking about um styles. So, if you
don't care about what style of video you
want, you have a community. Yeah, it's
it's it's again it's part of my Discord
community. It's people that get the
course. This is free. The PDF that I'm
showing you, which you can get, the link
is in bio, but then if you want to go
ahead and um take a step further and
learn a little more and level up, you
can get the course. And that's a
community that you get access to as
well. We have like 600 people in there.
Um, so, so that's a style modifier. Then
we have tone modifier. So serious,
playful, funny, inspirational. So those
are things that you can say when you're
adding your prompt because it's going to
add extra flavors to whatever video
you're creating. So we have uh mood,
which is dramatic, relaxed, energetic,
or calm. That's like mood modifiers. If
you say the environment is dramatic,
it's going to even if you don't know how
to describe it, you can just say
something like that. Um,
so here's an example. Cinematic shot of
a serious moment between a couple. Like
if you just add that, it's going to give
you a prompt. It's going to give you an
output of a cinematic shot. It's a
serious moment. And then maybe you want
to say the woman says to the man, blah
blah blah. The man says to the woman,
blah blah blah. So you just have to
guide it after this. Okay? You can't
just say this because this is too vague.
What are they going to do? What are they
going to do? You have to you have to
describe it.
If you want to roast my prompt on this
live, I'm okay with that. Prompt is in
your inbox.
Uh do you mind pasting it here in the
chat?
Because if I go to my inbox, I don't
want to have my screen showing
everything that I'm doing in my inbox.
So, I don't want to open that up right
now. If you want to see it on the live,
put put it in the chat and I'll get to
it.
All right. So, here's an example of a
cut to prompt. Okay. And we're going to
do some of these live, guys. So, if
you're sticking around here and you have
enough time, uh you're going to see some
of these live. You can also go to my uh
YouTube channel. I'm recording this
there. You can catch it later.
So, if you want to take uh your V3
prompts to a cinematic level with a
bunch of different angles, but remember,
it's only eight seconds, so don't go
crazy doing too many angles. I think top
is like three for me. I only change
angles three times if if that I like
just two to keep it simple. But it
allows you to shift the camera to
another angle in that same environment.
So that same world that exists when you
made the prompt, it's going to be the
same world when the the camera is
shifting. So for example, Bigfoot
running through a wide open field of
flowers. So here's my full prompt,
character setting, right? Lighting, all
that stuff that I just talked about.
Um, golden hour cinematic look. Cut to
closeup of Bigfoot's face. Heavy
breathing, focused eyes, same setting.
So, you don't have to really say same
setting because it already knows it. But
I just added that that so you guys when
you're reading this prompt, you
understand when you say cut to, it's
most likely going to give you the same
setting. I never had a different setting
happen when I when I started a shot
saying wide open field of flowers. So,
when it cut to his face, it's going to
be that same field. Why don't we try
this out right now? I'm going to copy
this. I never did this one before. This
is just an example that I wrote. Let's
put it to the test. All right.
All right. So, let's let's go put that
to the test. I just copied that prompt.
So, these are all the videos that I
created. So, all these are all these are
hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of
credits. So, let's create a new project
here. And then over here, we're going to
do a text to video prompt because this
is a text to video prompt that we're
talking about. You can do a image to
video prompt. Thank you for the gifts.
Thank you for the gift. Skin gloss.
Appreciate it. DK. And we have Let's
see. Any more gifts that I missed?
My name is Jeff. My name's Jeff is gone
now, right? Appreciate that though.
All right. So, I pasted the prompt over
here. If you guys want to turn your
screen sideways, I keep pointing the
wrong finger. This way, right here,
there's a little square. You can click
and your screen will be turn flipped
sideways. You can watch this
horizontally. If it's vertical, it's too
small for the Tik Tok people.
So, here, Bigfoot uh running through a
wide open field of flowers. Golden hour
light. Golden hour light. Cinematic
look. Cut to closeup of Bigfoot face.
So, here's here's what you're going to
do. Here you're going to put an action.
An action. What is it doing? Bigfoot
running through a wide open field of
flowers. Golden hour light cinematic
look. I think that's it. Let's just keep
it simple. And then cut to close-up of
Bigfoot's face. Heavy breathing focused
eyes. Same setting. And then let's put
an action. Now this is this is the
setting, right? This is the character
Bigfoot. What's the setting? It's the
open uh open field with flowers. Okay.
So what's the lighting?
golden hour. So it knows that to do like
that that golden hour kind of orange hue
in the sky. Now we need to describe
action and dialogue. So here's the
action. His heavy breathing, focused
eyes. So that's an action. And then
dialogue. He says,
I think I can stop now.
I don't know. I'm just going to make up
something.
Those guys
should be far behind me by now.
I think I can stop now. Those guys
should be far behind me by now. Okay,
let's see if that works right now. If it
doesn't, this is a perfect example of
how we can make it. We can see what's
going on with it. Okay, I smile. I I'll
go ahead and look at my DMs. I'll just
mute my screen. I just I know I can do
that. I forgot. I can just mute my
screen.
All right, let me go ahead and send this
prompt. And then while this is sending,
I'm going to go pull up your prompt,
your your DM. All right.
Oh, and the end, by the way, you might
want to add no captions.
You might want to add no captions to
this in case
it does those little caption. Sometimes
it does that.
All right. So, that's sending.
And then let's see. Go ahead and pull up
your your prompt here.
I'm going to leave this parked right
here.
All
[Music]
right. So, I got your prompt
and let's pull up your video, too.
Is this the video? I I want to I can't
see a response now, but if you can
answer there. If is is this video that
you linked what you got when you wrote
this prompt.
I'll probably know if I read it, but I
didn't read it yet.
Yes. Okay.
Got good music.
I also have my
Got my Duncan going.
All right, hold on. I got to pull up
your prompt.
So, if I go to notes,
actually, I'm going to put this prompt
in my screen so you guys can um can see
it better.
See the chat? Oh, you got the tapper
going. It's going crazy. That brings
more people in here.
Okay. Here's
here's a prompt of the Bigfoot in the in
the flowers.
We'll play that. We'll play that when I
have my screen shared for you guys. This
is your long prompt over here, man. I
can see already that's too long. I'll
tell you that right now.
Nice setup. Thank you. I appreciate it.
This is This is like This is what stops
people from the scroll. If I have the
setup like this, I notice that people
stop and the room fills up a little more
because people are um they have like
shiny object syndrome.
So once I once I hide it, they just see
this. They're like, "Yeah, I don't want
to learn."
All right.
Here's uh here's your prompt, my guy.
Let's go see your prompt here. Let's
let's let's watch that that um let's
watch this this video first. Let's see
how that happened. Oh, I got to put the
music down now.
All right. So, here's a prompt that we
wrote. Bigfoot running through a wide
open field of flowers. Golden hour.
Light cinematic. Um cut to Bigfoot's
face. Heavy breathing. Focused eyes.
Same setting. He says, "I think I can
stop now. Those guys should be far
behind me by now." No captions. All
right, let's watch it. He's running
through open fields. flowers cut to.
All right. So, it still gave us the
caption. You see,
it's again, it's not it's not something
you can control. I know the prompt was
good. I can't do anything else to make
it better. Now, one thing that you if
you don't like the the black bars, I
don't know if you can see it, but there
is cinematic bars. That happened because
I wrote cinematic. Okay? So if you don't
want to see that, sometimes I don't like
seeing those, you just take cinematic
out. So Bigfoot running through a wide
open field of flowers, golden hour
cinematic look. Take the cinematic out
and you have a full screen instead of a
black bar in bottom and the top. So this
is exactly how I envisioned it. Open
field, it runs.
All right. All right. So, that was an
example of a simple prompt. Here's what
our friend Smile wrote.
You know, before that, let me watch the
video. Let's watch the video together
cuz I I I'm looking at how long this is.
I might even get lost in it. So, let me
watch the video. I'm going to show you
guys a video that he wrote that he he
got from this prompt.
Can I make this full screen? It doesn't
matter. All right, let me see what what
you got here from this prompt. You made
it look so easy.
I don't know. I
I don't know that if I make it look
easy. I mean, I just type what I'm
thinking.
All right.
All right. So, I don't know how was
supposed to happen, but I'm going to
find out. I don't think that was
supposed to happen, right? I have
something in my
All right. Every time I get on the live,
something happens to my nose or my
throat.
Since I don't talk all day and then I
start talking.
Yeah, that's not how it's supposed to
go. All right.
I have water here. I don't have to keep
drinking the coffee and getting all my
mouth messed up.
Alpha Squatch. Yeah. So, why would you
why would you start it like that? I
don't I don't mean to be u to come out
swinging, but what does that mean? You
think like it knows what that means? It
think You think it knows the character
Alpha Squash? It doesn't.
It doesn't recognize like it doesn't
have me memory. So, it doesn't know what
that is. So, that's already throwing it
off.
Okay. Uh, a towering be I'm going to
just read it through and then I'm going
to go back and fix it. A towering beast
of muscle wrapped in a dark Oh, so
you're describing the character. Yeah,
that's not the format you should use
though. I don't know who. Yeah, go
anyway. The towering beast of a muscle
wrapped in a dark brown fur rocks a
tight black tank top eml blazing with
alpha squatch and bold distressed
lettering. His massive frame flexes with
every movement. A battered brown
military backpack hangs off his
shoulders at blink and a blinking GoPro
Hero 12 Black is strapped to his
forehead. His intense ape-like face
radiates character uh chaotic in
influencer energy. Glowing amber eyes on
the lens with the wild confident smirk.
He wears black puffer pants and looks
like he's always on
shout away from going viral. Man, what
did you what did you write this on? AI
Jack's a white flur.
Jack's Yeti, also of towering bees of
muscle, is equally imposing.
He sports the tactical vest labeled
jacks in bold block letters. He's
wearing a thick silver chain around his
neck and his icy blue eyes contrast his
snow white fur. GoPro placed on a rock
near the campfire. Also squash uh squats
behind a pan. Oh, Alpha. Alpha squats
behind a pan on the flames holding a
fish with two sticks. The fire is way
too hot.
Smoke is rising. Alpha.
And I'm already confused. But I I only
know cuz I saw what you wanted to make
it look like today. We're So this is my
suggestion to you, man. There's nothing
wrong with you want you want it to be
this specific. It's really cool that you
that you have that vision in mind.
Um,
but all this stuff
should not be done inside of
a text prompt. It's too complicated. So,
here's what I'm going to do. I'm going
to take your first
um biblical essay that you wrote.
So, we're going to do frames to video.
Okay, let me just make sure. Hold on one
second. Here's what I'm going to do. I'm
going to try to get that for you better.
Okay.
So, I did frames to video, right?
And then once I click that
frames of video, I click plus. And then
we're going to generate image right
here. We're going to click generate
image. Let's see if Gemini can make this
image. If not, you're going to have to
go to tragic PT and generate that image.
It's free. You can do three a day.
Thanks, Alex, for sharing the live. So
here here's what here's what this is
what the image generator is waiting for
a prompt. So it says text to image. So
this way you're going to write the
prompt.
Okay. So, I'm going to paste it. I'm
going to paste your um autobiography
here. Got a book. So, Alpha Squatch B.
So, all this stuff I'm not even going to
read it over. Okay. I'm going to just
send it. See what happens. Cuz there
it's so much wrong with it that I could
I want to spend like a whole hour fixing
it. So, here's what we're going to do.
And it's not your fault. AI wrote this
for you probably, right? I think you
said yes. So, yeah. So, Gemini sucks
with with image creation. See, it made a
little Well, that's not bad, though. See
the look.
Gemini is not as good as tragic PT. So,
that's what you start with, man. You
start with this. And make sure that you
you fix GoPro facing the camp. GoPro
facing the the setting. So, let's do
ultra realistic. Let me see. Let me
write that.
Where's the GoPro part? I got to fix
that. his intense look, blue eyes, GoPro
placed on a rock near the uh place on a
rock.
Um, lens facing
No, hold on. Place on the rock near the
campfire. And then when I write lens
facing the campfire, let's see if it's
smart enough to know that to flip the
camera the other way.
Looks like a GoPro commercial. if if
it's just chilling there like All right.
So, let me send that again.
Hi, what's your Discord handle? I would
love to learn how you did the square
thing you did last night.
Square thing.
What's What square thing did I do?
Um, I I have a Discord group. It's it's
behind the closed wall for for members
of my Discord group. But if you want to
ask me anything, it's Tik Tok DM is
better. I don't really check my Discord
DMs because it's I only have it open to
friends.
So, if you want to ask me a question,
just DM me on Tik Tok easier. You got
access to me easier that way. You did
live. What's Fire Square? Oh, oh, oh,
this the cube stuff, right? That's a
different AI. I can. Yeah, that's uh
that's that's called um that's runway.
That's runway. It's not this. Runway is
different. I haven't even talked about
runway yet because I'm still learning
it. Uh can you can you friend me? I'll
pay for it
on Discord. My Discord um my Discord is
DJI Chaos just like my name here.
Yeah, just let me know what you think
and it'll figure it out. I can I can I
can just help I can just teach you how
to do it
then you can make as many as you want.
You don't have to pay anybody. All
right, man. So, smile that it's not
coming out, man. It's not coming out
with visuals that we want. Right. So,
let's go and uh let me open up my uh my
chat GPT. Thank you for the tabs on the
screen. I have an idea of who that is.
Always helping out. Appreciate it.
All right, sir. Let's go. Let's go to
Chad GPT for your for your prompt here.
And then at the end of this, I'm going
to write you have to write a CHP prompt.
In the end, you have to write this 69
image ratio.
6:9 image ratio
because otherwise it's going to give you
like a square image or or portrait
looking image like a 916. You want a
16-9 because the goal is for you to put
it into Google Flow.
Um
well that's creating that. Let's go back
to this. Okay. Oh, look at this. This is
pretty cool. But the GoPros Let me see
if the GoPro Yeah, the GoPro didn't face
the other way.
So, what was supposed to happen? What
was supposed to be the dialogue? Let me
see.
Oh, I think I I didn't
I erased the dialogue. I got to go back
to the DMs here.
I was trying to make something cool last
night. Look at this.
I was I wanted the tiger to chase me but
didn't like follow behind, you know.
All right, let me pull up your DM again.
I'm leaving that playing on purpose
while I get the DMs pulled up.
Uh, let's see. Message
So, we're helping here. We're helping
our our
one of our um our friends here that it's
in the Discord in the in the in the
course and also a longtime follower here
of my account. By long time, I mean
probably at least at least a month
because I'll only be here two months.
Okay. So, let's go back to his prompt
here.
I'm going to paste that into my notes so
I don't lose it again. I want to see
what the action was supposed to do
because I already have the look, right?
We already have I know what your setting
is supposed to look like.
I have I have the setting idea. It looks
It looks good. Now I just have to figure
out what you want as far as um
the action. Let's see if Tragy PT is
finished. Yeah. No, it didn't even
it didn't even give me a 16-9 ratio.
What the heck is going on? But look,
man, if you want to create a a
consistent character and you want them
to look like this, you can always look
him make him look like this now because
it's it's inside tragpt and it remembers
your guy. It remembers your characters.
So, if you always wanted that look,
right? Obviously, we don't like that
look. I don't like it. I don't know
about you. So, let me do it again. Same
thing.
Where's he at? Is he still here? What
are you thinking? What are you thinking?
Smile.
So, let's do a landscape
image. Just one more. One more
reinforcement. 69 image ratio. Lens 69
69 image ratio landscape
um orientation.
Just another doubling doubling my my
instructions.
Oh, let me take out the ultra realistic
look because Tragedy PT doesn't need
this.
Tragic PT doesn't need that. So, let's
go ahead and and read what your what
your action is now. So, I I can just
have that in my head and we can do it.
Um,
where was the prompt start?
The prompt stopped at
The prompt stopped at the fire is too
hot. Smoke is rising. Okay. So after
that is what I left out. The fire start
smoke is rising. Alpha. Okay. I see.
So forget all this. We don't need that.
Cancel. So after the image is done, this
is what we're going to put in here. So
after the setting is done, remember the
setting is what we just um we're trying
to create now. So all that is is going
to be gone. We don't need that anymore.
After we get our happy results that we
are happy with, after we get the results
we're happy with, we don't need all
that. We only need the next part, which
is what I the remaining of your prompt.
Alpha into the GoPro. Today, we're
cooking wild caught trout alpha style.
No rules, just instinct.
All right. So, take out the M dash jacks
off camera.
What does that mean? Off camera. Flat.
Like, what? What's flat? It's literally
on fire.
Oh, like like his his um manner like the
way he says it
like monologue. It's literally on fire.
The fish burn uh bursts into flame.
Alpha panics and flips it out of the pan
into the dirt. Alpha is still filming.
It's got flavor. Extra bark crust. Yeah,
man. Look. So many too many action. So,
this is already like 10 seconds. This is
This is already 10 seconds worth of
stuff. You got to split it. Jax walks
into frame holding a perfectly grilled
fish on the stick. Yeah. So, this is
like two videos. The action is is too
much. Let's see. Let's go back to
Come on, GPT. Give me the image already,
man. Taking too long. All right. So,
it's insisting on making this guy look
like half human.
Let's be good with that for now. Okay. I
don't It's not a big something in there
is telling it to make it look like that
and I don't want to I don't want to go
through the prompt again and read it.
Let's just pretend you're you're okay
with this. Let's save it.
All right. So, I'm saving this.
So, I clicked save.
It might be cool to have him look like
that, but it's I know your character is
already established and you know your
video is going to be very different if
you use him like this. What you can do
is take a screenshot of one of your of
your videos already and go in here and
say
these this is how these guys are
supposed to look.
All right. So meaning like for example I
go to your page right now. Where are you
at?
So
I don't like the way they look over
here. They look too 3D cartoon. Let me
see one that the prompt got it nice and
right.
Yeah, that one. He looks like a raccoon.
All right, so watch this, man. All
right, so this this is a good look right
there. So this is what you're going to
do. If you want him to look like that,
play it without the play in the front.
All right. So, I I'm doing the
screenshot.
All right. So, I did a screenshot of
that. Right now, I'm going to go to
character on chat JPT
and I'm going to I'm going to paste that
image
right here
and I'm going to read I'm going to
reprompt it again.
And then I'm going to say
use this as a reference for how
my characters
look. So all I did was take a screenshot
and then I pasted it into and I pasted
it right here into chatgpt into an image
into the image box. You following?
Yeah. Mid Journey is also paid. I don't
want to use Mid Journey. Use reference
for how my charact as a reference for
how my character looks. All right. So,
let's go send it. So, I I loaded that
and I put the image and I want to resend
it.
Let's see if it gets it right. If it
doesn't, it's because I did it in the
same window. Remember how I told you it
remembers the character? So, you have to
start a new chat. I shouldn't I I was
sloppy with this. I should not have
started this prompt in this chat because
it's going to be corrupted by this look.
It kind of knows already what it's
supposed to look like. So, I'm I'm gonna
confuse it. Let's see what happens,
though. If it doesn't work, it's because
you have to start a new window, a new
session.
Oh, you got it back. Okay.
All right. So, let me go back again to
Did everybody else lose the audio too or
just him? Let me know because if if if
you all lost it and it's probably my
mixer because it's a new mixer and the
first day I used it. It was a buzz and I
fixed it but now I'm still kind of Yeah,
but did you always heard me? I didn't go
away, right? Maybe it was just him.
Maybe his Wi-Fi like dropped or
something.
Okay, cool. All right, so
Hold on, folks. Hold on.
Alpha into GoPro camera. Today we're
cooking a while. Oh, I already read
this. Okay, I decided it was too much.
So, let's see if I can get the image
right and then we'll break it down
into u two videos.
It's like watch watching paint dry.
Literally like watching pixels dry.
Watching pixels dry over here with this
this strategy taking this long.
It's funny how we are so impatient now.
Huh? Before couldn't even do this stuff.
All right. He looks half human already.
I can see it.
Yeah, it corrupted. I I shouldn't have
done it in the same session. Yeah, look
at it. I can accurately see from the
what I'm seeing right there that he's he
looks he doesn't look like that at all.
Yeah. Dang it.
After all that waiting twice.
Okay. So, here's what we're going to do.
New session.
I'm going to do it right, man.
I can't I can't just compromise like
that.
All right. Try GPT2.
DJI zero. Let's let's try to get a
revenge on us now.
Okay. So, here's a new new session.
Let's get back to this right here.
Another screenshot cuz that one was
another screenshot.
Boom.
So, a screenshot on the on the computer.
I don't even know if I to tell you how I
did it. It's like control
control altshift.
I don't even know how to tell you. My
fingers automatically go to it.
That's how you take a screenshot on the
computer. I can't even tell you exactly
what press buttons to press. I just know
it by just not even thinking about it.
They just go to it. So, here's a
screenshot. I took it and I control V
it. I pasted it.
All right, let's try it again, guys. If
this doesn't work, you just keep trying,
man. May maybe mid journey. Somebody
said it's better. So, if you want to
really invest in getting these
characters good, do that. For now, let's
pretend I have the perfect image so we
can get keep going here. Okay, let's
pretend I have the perfect image.
Um,
Benito Effect says it's him. What's
Who's him on YouTube? He said that. So,
Alpha. Um, so who's Alpha again? It's
the one with the black shirt
and Jax is the is a yeti, right? Okay.
All right, here we go. Um,
Alpha the Bigfoot because now it doesn't
know who Alpha is. So, you got to tell
you got to tell V3 who Alpha is. Alpha
the Bigfoot says,
"Today we're cooking wild caught trout.
Alpha style. No rules, just instincts.
Today we're cooking alpha." Hold on.
Today we're cooking wild caught trout
alpha style. No rules, just instinct.
So, brother, that's 5 seconds right
there. That's 5 seconds, man. You have 3
seconds left.
Let's say I counted too fast. Let's say
4 seconds. Okay, let's give it let's
give it some grace. And then Jack's off
camera. What? I'm sorry. You said flat.
I don't know what that I I You might
have answered me. I don't know what that
means, but I'll leave it. I don't know
what flat means.
Um
I I said it and then I never looked over
to see the answer. It's literally on
fire. The fish bursts into flame.
Alpha panics and flip it on the p uh out
the pan onto the dirt.
All right. So, this is this is this is
what I'm going to try to push it with
right there. Delete everything else.
Let's do this first. Let's do this one
and then the second part. We'll we'll
take it from we'll take it once we get
this first part right cuz it was way too
much.
I think we're I think I'm confident that
this will um TP gave me that prompt in
the prompt. Yeah, I'm gonna delete it
then. I don't know what that what that
means. Flat.
Thank you for the tap. I appreciate it.
You got to replace the battery on that
thing. How long does it take to charge?
Thank you for the gifts, by the way.
Lightning heart.
Save the rest of the prompt. Yeah, I
saved it.
I saved it. Thank you for the reminder.
Oh, guys, tragic PT is not not working
for me today, man. Look at this. It
looks like claimation.
Let's let's let's spray that. I think V3
is actually going to make it more
realistic. So, let's just use this.
Let's just use this because I think it's
going to it's going to improve the
quality of his face on on V3.
At least it's a closer look, right?
better than than the cartoon look we had
before. So, it's a closer look to what
you have. I'm comparing them. I think V3
is going to animate them a little
better. So, just forgive Trap PT right
now. It's not feeling well.
Lately, it's been grainy. It's been
giving grainy results. So, we're going
to upload.
I'm going to paste the results right
here.
And then here's what you can do. You can
leave the black bars on the side because
chat GPT does not make a completely
landscape image ever. It doesn't do a
169. It does like a less ratio. You can
do this.
You can crop in like this and make it
full
or
you can just leave the black bars on the
side because then when you get your when
you get your output, what you can do is
pinch it in a little more on Tik Tok and
crop the sides. That's that's what I do.
It even gives you a better So, let me
see how you post your videos. Let me see
how you post them.
Oh, it's different on my computer. Okay.
So, you post them sideways, right? You
post the landscape. On the computer, it
makes it look nice, but on the phone,
it's going to squish them, right? So,
you just pinch a little more. It's going
to make it taller. It's going to make it
a little taller, which is better. So,
here's um here's a So, let's crop and
save that.
So, it's loaded.
The image is loaded now. This is this is
the prompt. Alpha the Bigfoot says,
"Today we're cooking Alpha style. No
rules, just anything." Jax the Yeti.
The off camera thing, it doesn't work.
Let me see if yours worked the first
time.
Oh, no. It does work. Okay.
Yeah. See, it didn't work. It jumped to
it. It doesn't like off camera. I I
tried that so many times. Let's just
keep it in there, though. I don't care.
Let's see. Let's keep it in. See if I
can get it, Jack. It doesn't like speech
or dialogue
off camera. You know what I mean?
Take the flat out. It's literally on
fire. The fish bursts into flame flames.
Alpha panics and flips out.
How about this? Jack's the yeti because
it What's the point of saying he's a
yeti? He's not even on the in the image.
Um Oh, he's in the image right here. So,
when you say off camera, he's already in
the image. So,
uh Jack the Yeti
watches
and says he just sitting there watching.
It's literally on fire.
The fish bursts into flames. Alpha
panics and flips it. Okay. Flips the pen
to the dirt. Let's send it.
Let's send it with the image in there.
That took a little bit. See, these
problems take time. But if you like it,
you don't mind it. You know, if you
don't like what if you like doing this
stuff, I like doing this stuff. That's
why I don't rush.
Has USB cords.
What does that mean? Did I miss a
conversation here? Control Shift S. Let
me see if it was that. See, I I think
about it and I just lost it. I just I
can't think about it. Let's see.
See, I messed it up. My brain glitched.
Okay, I got it. I can't I can't look at
it or think about it. So, it's control
Windows S. That's how you take a
screenshot. Control Windows S. the
little windows um
on your keyboard.
So you sent the image from chatpt with
the prompt. So you sent the image from
chat GPT with the prompt. Yes, with the
with the prompt after
all the setting was already you know
like I used the setting on chat GPT and
then I used action just on
just on um V3. All right, let's pray
this works. Let's see. Let's see if the
characters are saying the right line.
And if not, we're going to see what's
wrong and fix it.
All right. So, we did too much. The I
told you it was too much, right? The
flipping pen didn't happen. Alpha panics
and flips it out of the pan into the
dirt. That didn't happen.
What do you think about that? Is that
besides the look of the character? I'm
not thrilled with how the Bigfoot looks,
but look is exactly what you ask for.
So now
to get that second part that I missed,
we're going to go into add scene.
I don't know why he crossed his arm like
he's annoyed.
So, if if you wanted to run this again,
you can try running it again, but let's
pretend that you liked it.
So, now what we're going to do is we're
going to do add to scene.
And then here, you're going to find that
frame where it left off.
He was supposed to have a pen with it,
didn't he? Not supposed to be on the
stick like that, is it? Let me see. Um,
tracks the white also to muscle equal is
imposing. He Okay.
Alpha squats behind the pan on the
flames holding a fish. Oh, okay. So, the
pan is Oh, it was missed by the image.
It's good enough. It's on the stick,
right?
I will be at the pan of flames holding
the fish to stick fires too hot. Smoke
is rising.
And then I'm looking at the prompt. You
don't have to you don't see it here on
my screen, but I see it. Today we're
cooking slowly on fire. The fish burns
in bursts into flame. Alpha panics and
flips it out of the pan into the dirt.
So then
let's just copy that part. So here, this
is where we left off, right?
Let's say this is this this is where
he's holding right here. Look at his
face. He's like panicked. And there's
the other the yeti is like, "Oh, what's
going on?" So, if this is a scene that
you want to start with your next video,
you you stop the cursor right here. You
stop the cursor right here. Don't keep
going until the end because then like
the action is already gone here. So,
this is where you're going to stop it
right here where they're both freaking
out right there. And you just hit you
just see the plus sign up here. You got
to do this in your computer, man. I
don't know about the phone. I don't know
if it's it's going to be too much for
you to do. So, click the plus right
there. Save frame as asset. It's going
to save it in your brow in your in your
library right here. Okay. Saved it right
there. So, now this is what you do.
You get out.
You click right here on the bottom where
it says generate a prompt. Click plus.
load that frame and you're going to
continue your action here. So, Alpha,
I'm going to write again the Bigfoot
panics and flips it. It doesn't know
what it is because it's a new prompt.
And throws the fish into the dirt in the
on the uh into
just going to put on the dirt
or on the on the on the ground. Say on
the ground.
Alpha the Bigfoot panics and throws the
fish on the ground.
So, you don't have to say Alpha's still
filming because the camera is already
here. So, we don't need all this.
Alpha's still filming. And then
it's uh it's got flavor. Extra bark
crust. Jax walks into frame.
So, this is doesn't make sense now cuz
Jax is already in frame, right? Jack
rocks into frame holding a perfectly
grilled fish on the stick and just
shakes his head. So, he was supposed to
be off frame. You see how this all got
messed up? because Drax is supposed to
be off frame saying this is on you know
this is um it's literally on fire or
whatever. So if you were to regenerate
that image just just say into the chat
into the chat GPT prompt right here just
say
watch
click on the image you have to click on
the image. Okay so if you're going to do
a modification on chatbt don't write
under under where it says ask anything
this way. Oh my my hand's cut off. You
see the box right here where it says ask
anything. You can't see it cuz it's
cropped out the bottom. But don't don't
type it on onto the main window. Click
on the image. And then here you're going
to say again, but
remove
the Yeti.
And then it's going to should give you
the same image without the Yeti.
69 image ratio. So then you would start
with that image.
You start with the image, man. And then
instead of saying the Yeti says, you
just say a voice off camera says because
we don't need to know in that first
scene, the 8 seconds, we don't need to
know who says it because it doesn't
care. So in that once it creates the
whole scene again without the Yeti,
you're going to put that into chat into
Google Flow. You do the same thing we
just did, but just say an off camera
voice says,
"I wasn't able to generate the image
this time. Something wrong or something
wrong. Uh, can resend the request?
Try again. Let's try it again. Let's go
back here. So, let's finish this prompt
right here. Alpha the Bigfoot panics and
throws a fish into the ground. It's It's
got flavor. Extra barcross. Jax walks
into frame. So, we got to change this a
little bit now because we already
started the wrong foot by having Jax in
frame already. I didn't realize the
whole story. Like, I I'm doing this
live, so it's kind of hard to to try to
get everything right. Jax walks into
frame holding a perfectly grilled fish
on the stick.
I'm gonna make the story a little
different. Now look, watch.
So after he says that, I'm going to do
this. Cut to
Jack's
the Yeti cuz obviously he's already on
there, right? Medium shot
holding a
perfectly
grilled
fish
on the stick.
He says
he says, let me see what he says again.
Uh
oh, he doesn't say anything. He just
shook his head.
So, let's make him say this.
Mine
turned out perfectly fine.
All right, let's change the story a
little bit. Alpha the Bigfoot panics and
throws a fish on the ground. It's got
flavor, extra bark crust,
cut two jacks. What What does he do
after that? Because it's kind of dry.
He's going to say that and do like
shrug. What is he gonna do?
I know what he's gonna say. Oh well.
Don't put dot dot dot. It doesn't work.
It's going to grunt or something weird.
Just say, "Oh well, it's got flavor."
Extra buck crust. Cut to Jack the Yeti.
Medium shot holding a perfectly grilled
fish on the stick. He says, "Mine turned
out perfectly fine." And then
I'm going to put he smiles.
And then obviously we're going to do no
captions.
All right. All right, guy. Let's go.
Let's send it.
Let's send it to see how that works.
Okay. And then in the in the editing,
sorry that took so long.
It's literally on fire.
Yeah, I just changed it up a little bit
so it made sense. I don't know if it's
what you wanted, but I'm just showing
you how you get it to do exactly what
you want. Um, in the editing, you're
going to get two videos, right? When you
upload it to Tik Tok, edit in the Tik
Tok app, okay? Because a lot of these
videos, if you edit outside of Tik Tok,
like on Cap Cut or if you edit in
another app and then you bring it into
Tik Tok, it's going to label it as
unoriginal.
It might label it as unoriginal. there's
a high chance that it will because it's
AI. But if you if you because it thinks
like it's so high quality that the
algorithm sees it and it's like, "Oh,
it's one of those AI recycled videos."
If you edit in the Tik Tok app, the
metadata is going to be different. It's
going to know that it was edited in
there and therefore it's going to know
that it's original. Um, it does help you
even if you have to file like a like a
like an appeal, it helps. They'll know
that you edited this inside the Tik Tok
app. So, in anyway, I mentioned that
because in the app, you're going to cut.
You see this little arrow? Anything to
the right, you're going to cut it. So,
you're going to slide that until you
have the perfect match because that's
that's the ending point of that first
video. And then the second video starts
at the at this frame right here. Watch.
This is that frame that we paused. So,
in editing, you're going to cut that
out. The rest is junk. This is where
your video starts right here where that
frame ended. So, let's pray now. Let's
let's watch it. Okay. Let's see if it
worked. I'm putting my money where my
mouth is.
didn't throw it. Oh, that's not the
yeti. That's not the yeti at all. That's
not the yeti at all. So, let's let's
let's see what went wrong here.
He didn't throw it into the ground,
first of all. So, that's that's not our
fault. This is the like this is what I'm
saying by the AI's fault. Okay? When we
said throw it into the ground, he didn't
do that. So, there's nothing else he can
do besides try it again.
Or you can say extra charcoal or
something if it's burnt. If you can't
really get them to throw on the ground,
you just make another line. Make another
line. So why did this not show me?
This could be a third character, bro.
Let's go with it. It's a third
character. All right. It's a It's a
guest.
Let's watch the whole thing.
So here here's that. So I got out of
there. So here's that that second one
right here. So you literally would just
download the first one right here.
Download it. 720. Done. And then you
download the second one. 720. Done.
Import it into your Tik Tok app. And
then right here, you're gonna
Which one's the first video?
I cropped it before. He said literally
on fire.
the voice. So, number one, the voice is
different. Number two, user error. I
cropped it. Remember, I took this shot.
That was before he says it's literally
on fire.
So, that was my mistake. I should have
started the frame cuz I got I wanted it
to be where the fish was still in his
hands and not down.
So, at this point, you would have to
take it after he says it. You know, take
a frame after he says that. You know
what I mean? And then you rebuild it
like I showed you before. But this is
the part where this is the part where we
did everything right.
Meaning the prompt we wrote it right,
but then it didn't throw it on the
ground. So, oh well. So, look. Alpha of
the Bigfoot panics and throws a fish on
the ground. He didn't throw it. That's
all you can do is ask for it. Let's try
it again. Ready? Let's copy this.
Let's Let's load that frame again and
then paste the same thing. I'm not going
to change anything because I did
everything right. Alpha the big foot
penis and throws a fish on the ground.
Oh, I got it's got flavor extra bar plus
cut to Jax the Yeti. Medium shot holding
her. So, why did Jax become a different
character? Maybe I didn't give the
directions.
Maybe I didn't give directions of who
Jax was. I just figured he would see it.
Right here it says Jax. That's the dude.
That's the Yeti. I paper throw this fish
in the ground. Oh well.
How about this? Cut to
medium shot
of the other character. I should say
other character cuz if it knows that
this is the character, the other
character must be this guy. I don't
know.
All right. This is What are you using?
Yeah. Switch the quality. That's 100
points, my boy. I'm not doing that.
That's 100 credits. We're going to keep
it at 20 and be happy about that. I'm
not burning my credits on the 100. I'm
using Flow, guys. I'm using Flow. And if
you guys want a free guide on how to do
this, okay, how to write these prompts
and how to create these videos,
check out my free guide. I'm going to
show you right now while that video is
baking, while it's cooking.
Thank you for the tabs. I appreciate
that.
Okay, so here's a free guide that I made
for you guys. If you want to get it,
it's in my bio. Go to my bio. The link
is in there. There's a link tree link.
You can go ahead and click on that first
link that says um how to create V3
videos. And then in that page, you're
going to get two options. A paid option
to get the video course. And this is my
PDF course that has 80% of what I teach
because obviously I have to say the
other 20% more advanced stuff to my for
my course. Okay. So, this is everything
that you're going to get with the free
PDF. I don't require anything besides
you going into um the link and then
getting it behind the the This it's
called a It's where WH hop is
where I I host this PDF at. So that's
where you you go and click in my bio and
then go to the um go to the free PDF
option. So it's an introduction. V3
explained. If you don't know what V3 is,
I explain it. I wrote it myself. So it's
not like it's not it's created by human
for humans. Okay? I know it's AI stuff,
but this is I wrote it because I didn't
want an AI to write what I know because
it doesn't know exactly everything that
I know. So, it took me a week to write
it and I finally put it together today
into a PDF format. So, introduction, we
have the essentials and then this is
going to be the most valuable part for
you. If you're if you already know what
this, you know, introduction and
essentials already know all this, just
skip it to the prompting. And this is
the part that a lot of people uh
struggle with and this is what I'm
covering today. And then the level up is
where I show you what's possible. And
then that's the 20% that I leave out.
Okay? If you want creative controls, if
you want to learn how to do cut two
shots, if you want to learn how to do
frames to uh video, how to do
ingredients to video, you can either
catch my lives that I teach for free, or
if you want it um pre-recorded and and
ready to go, bundled up. It's just what
I teach on the live, but pre-recorded,
organized. I took the time to put it
together. nicely for you to learn. And
that's when you can go and um you can
get the course. $25 by the way, but it's
not this is not paid. This is free. What
I'm showing you right now, it's free. So
then you got usage cases. This is how
you can use it to make money to if
you're a teacher, you want to do stuff
in education, how you can use for social
media. It's all down here. So here we
got systems. It's very organized. Again,
I I designed it and created it myself. I
use Canva, by the way, for for creating
this look. If you like the look, it's a
PDF, but I made it in Canva. Okay, so
here's my here's my idea for a coffee
company. If I ever create a I like I
like iced coffee if you guys can't tell.
If you guys can't tell, uh I like iced
coffee. So here, if I were to make a ice
coffee company, this is what I would do.
I will create an ad using V3 for my DJI
Beans. Okay, that's my fictional coffee
company. So then this is an example of
how educators can use it to teach kids
about photosynthesis. For example,
I I literally made a video about it and
it came out pretty cool. It's you can't
watch the video here because I didn't
upload it. It's a PDF. Um
yeah, so I'm just scrolling through it.
So this step-by-step guide walks you
through um mastering the world's most
powerful AI tool. You learn how to craft
effective prompts, avoiding common
mistakes. So, this is all the stuff that
you're going to get for free in this
PDF.
I originally list I originally made this
guys. I was going to sell this uh guide
on Etsy. I was going to sell it for like
10 bucks because that's a lot of work.
It took me a long time to build it and
two like everything that I learned in
two months is in here. So, I originally
wanted it for Etsy, but I'm like I
there's no point. I might as well make
it free to help people create these um
because I don't think anybody's even
going to buy this if I put it up there.
I don't know. I just decided to just
make it for free because you guys are
are a good community here and you guys
support my stuff. So, I I don't mind
taking time to to do this stuff for you
guys. All right, so let's go back to my
um
let's go back to that prompt.
All right, Drax. Let's see what Drax is
doing right now. Our friend still here
or did he leave? Are you still here?
Thank you, Logan and uh DK and Smile and
Lexic. Lexus and Trash Panda and Alex
for being our top five watchers here
sticking around with us. 43. Wow, guys.
I'm not even watching the likes. That
tapper. Somebody's got a tapper here.
And it's our friend uh Skin Gloss aka
DK. She's over here using the tapper.
She got 43K likes on that live for me. I
appreciate that. All right, this is a
redo of our prompt, the second part.
Let's play it.
So see same prompt different look same
prompt again it's not my fault this is
this is happens to you guys happens to
me watch
it he threw it down which is a plus
I like this part I love this part
actually
and then they laugh but then he says
So, that is a that is a flaw. But here,
I I I like I like this so much that I'd
keep this and just cut it right there.
Cut it right here.
No, wait. Wait. You know what I mean,
right? Watch.
Cut it right there. And then if you
really want that last part where he
says, "Mine turned out perfectly fine,"
you can you have two choices.
redo the prompt again and see if he can
get it right or create a whole new video
that makes him
say the the Yeti make mine turn out
perfectly fine. Sometimes this stuff is
just it takes time. So if you want a
cinematic story the way you want it,
that's why I go through that all the
time. I made an entire little I made an
entire little cartoon. If you guys think
this was a lot of work for like a
10-second video that might get like 200
views,
then you might you might just want to uh
find another hobby because sometimes
that happens, okay? Or you might want to
find another way to make money because
if you're going to do these videos and
you don't love it and you're willing to
take the risk, you can get a viral
video. I made a quick video uh on a
Saturday,
this video right here, and it got three
million views.
If you're watching this vertical, guys,
if you click on that um the square, you
can see it full screen. But so if you're
watching the vertical, it's cut off. But
this video right here,
that took literally like not even 20
minutes from beginning to end. And I've
made videos that took me three, four
hours and it didn't get close. It got
500 views instead of instead of three
million. So, it's it's a hobby. You just
got to have fun with it. And you can
make money. Like this video right here.
It made me $70 and it took me about 45
minutes, not even an hour. Watch this
video.
So, I got 300,000 views. And because I
get paid for for videos that are over a
minute, uh that brought me monetization
rewards of um about $70, 65 or something
like that. So anyway, this is another
one that I made. I'm going to play a
whole clip for you. And if you like if
you like this style, I hope that was
helpful, bro. Smile. Let me see if um
Tragic PT helped us with this. Look,
man, if you want that first frame again,
this is what your first frame would be.
Okay? The Yeti is not in it. The Yeti is
not in. Remember we said remove the
Yeti. Look,
I like that better, though.
I'm gonna save this. Watch this. I'm
gonna save this. And then we're gonna go
back and we're going to redo that first
prompt. Uh, bro, we're going to redo
that. We're going to go in here. We're
going to take this. Let's see if it
works. We're going to upload that second
image without the Yeti.
And then right here, we're going to
write Alfa the Bigfoot says, "Today
we're going to cook wild caught trout."
Um, alpha style, no rules. Instead of
saying Jack, uh, Jack the Yeti watches
and says,
I'm gonna say an offscreen voice. An
offscreen voice
says it's literally on fire.
The fish bursts into flame.
The Bigfoot panics. I'm going to say the
Bigfoot instead of Alpha.
It doesn't care what it name is.
But remember that that last part with
where he flipped it into the dirt, it
was um it was cut off because it was too
long. But let's try it. Let's just send
it like this. So an offscreen charact
voice says it's literally on fire. The
fish burst into flame. The uh Bigfoot
panics and flips out and flips flips it
out of the pan. I'm going to say the
fish
fish out of the pan into the into the
dirt. Okay, send it.
So, we redid that first one without the
character. Okay, let's see if the
offscreen works. So, I never had luck
with offscreen stuff. Where was I at
now, guys? Um, okay. So, I'm going to
show you a quick
How do you Um, do you only stream on
landscape or both? Both. Do you only
stream on landscape or both?
Both. You can watch it both, right?
You're supposed to be watching it both.
You can watch it vertical or landscape.
Hold on one second. All right. I'm going
to show you guys I'm going to show you
guys a
a complete cartoon animation I created
using VO.
And
you can do the same thing. And I'll show
you how to do that in a second. Let me
let me play the Let me play the video
for you. While I'm doing something else
and this is cooking here, let me play
the video of the animation that I
created and then
uh we're going to discuss it. Here we
go. See if it works.
Are you guys ready? Let me You want to
see the animation? Type five in the
chat. Type number five in the chat. I'll
play the animation for you. Let's get
some engagement in here. If you're
watching here and you're liking this
stuff, you want to see a I think it was
like 60 seconds animation that I made,
type five in the chat and we're going to
get started on it.
All right. So, five people type five.
That's enough, right? All right. Here we
go. Let's see if this is it. I haven't
played in a long time.
All
right. So, that was completely created
using VO2.
Not even three. This is VO2. It only
takes 10 credits to make each video. And
in there, there's about 16 clips. It was
all made in here. And I'll go back to
the alpha one second. Hold on. It was
all made in here, guys. Look. It was all
made in here. I'll show you the entire
project file. And if you want a step by
step on how to how I made it, I walk you
through every step. Uh I suggest you
first let me show you first the the the
actual creation floor which is right
here. So I created each clip in here
so much and my computer's like
struggling to keep up with the images.
Okay, I created it all in here using
prompts
and then I did a AI voice over
using another software which I teach you
all that in the in the course. But the
point is you can make all this stuff.
You can sell I sold some videos like
this to local businesses, okay?
Explaining their products, explain their
videos. You can sell it to to local
businesses. You can post it on social
media. Local businesses will reach out
to you. Like I had so many DMs. I I miss
so many of them because I get people
asking me to make these videos for their
business. It's just here in the chat
now. Somebody said, "I'll pay you to
make something for me." And I said,
"Just DM me. I don't know if they're
still here or not, but I get I I
literally can't accommodate all those
requests. Maybe I should like start a
group and you guys can freelance for me
in there, okay? I'll take a cut. Maybe
you learn and then you you I'll get you
the jobs and you you can get it and I'll
make like some commission because I I
get so many requests for these things."
But here's what I made using that V2. I
just showed you all that video that you
just watched. It was all made here.
Look, all made here. And the the way
that you make this, you're going to go
to um ingredients to video. And then
you're going to pick your characters
that you pre-made using chat GPT. So all
those characters right here, see them?
Every time I change clothes in that in
that in that film, in that little clip,
I had a different character made for
that scene. So I didn't make the scenes
on chat. just made the character and
then Chad Chippy I mean um and then V3
which is this V2 I mean sorry V2 V2 made
these for me and if you're wondering
like what does that mean V2 V3 on this
engine it's called Google flow you have
V3 which is the version that's realistic
with audio and then you have V2 which is
like more animated stuff with no audio
so all my videos have no audio watch
see I'm playing it there's no audio on
it it's just literally for visuals then
you can take all that put it together
into a whole storyline that you use
another AI to do the voice over for you
or you can do the voice over yourself if
you like your voice or if you like, you
know, want to have somebody voice over
your kids. Maybe your kids want to do a
little storyboarding and then you can
have them narrate it. That would be
awesome. My daughter wants to create
something and I haven't had uh the time
to sit down and create something with
her, but she has a whole script that she
wants to recreate. She's only um she's
only eight, so she's going to have fun
once we sit down and make her
storyboard. So, here's what everything
looks like. And here's what I suggest
for you. Okay? If you want to learn how
to do this, it's in my course. But
before you do that, before you do that,
why don't you just first of all see if
this stuff is for you. See if you like
it by going to my profile, click on the
link tree link right here. And I might
get a warning from Tik Tok because I'm
showing this on the live. They kind of
know that I'm directing people out of
it. But stay here. Don't leave yet.
Don't leave my live yet. Or get flagged
that I'm it knows that people are
leaving. So, and clicking on my links.
Don't do that yet. So once you go to the
link tree, click on here on the first
link. Okay, that first link right here.
You see this free guide,
I'm sorry, free guide right here. The
first one, free learners guide. Click on
that and you're going to hit hit off uh
get offer and you're going to you're
going to download the PDF that I have
for you right here. So, and then see see
if you like the learning style,
the teaching style that I get into right
here. So, it's a how many pages is it?
It's a 30-page PDF. It took me it took
me two months to learn this stuff
probably a thousand hours. Okay? And
then I had to sit down and and write it.
Though this is not AI made. This is
written by me every word. You might see
some spelling mistakes in there. I try
to run it by AI and say, "Can you do a
grammar check, uh, spelling check or
whatever, but you might find some stuff
in there that's that's not perfect." But
because I I it's a free resource, okay?
I wasn't I wasn't going to like ask for
my uh my English teacher to grade it for
me. So, I just sent it. I just ripped it
up. I read it once. It looked good. So,
all this stuff is free. People charge
you $20 for this. I can go right now. I
can go right now on Etsy and look for a
PDF guide on this. And I'm sure it's
going to be something expensive. Okay.
So, and I'm going to play that video, by
the way, that I just created. We're
going to show you guys.
Let me see something, by the way. Let me
So, let me look at I'm on Etsy right
now. I'm going to do V3 prompt guide.
I don't want to see the stuff on on
Etsy, folks. I don't want to see you
guys ripping off my stuff and and
selling it there. All right. I literally
will find you and I'm going to get some
money out of you if you do that because
I do have a company and I do have
attorneys. So, that's that's not
something you want to mess with. Don't
be ripping up my stuff. Ripping off my
stuff. So, here we go. I had to I had to
do a f cease and decease on something
just just this morning.
Somebody was taking my videos and
running ads with it and
it's ongoing, but we're going to get
something going there. Some
compensation. I'll update you guys once
it's done because I don't want to
discuss it's it's in process right now,
so I don't want to discuss it. So, here
some people are selling these things.
$25.
Okay, here's another one. 20 bucks.
Great. Good for them, right? But I don't
I don't hate on that. That's cool.
They're making money. I'm just showing
you guys the value that you're going to
get on that P free P free PDF.
Probably everything that they have in
here is what I'm going to teach you in
there. So, and then if you want to get
the if you want to get the course at
$25, that's a that's something you can
do, too. But I'm not I'm not pushing you
for that at all. I'm just I just want
you to download the free guide so you
can learn it. And then if you want a
step by step because you're having
difficulties or whatever, then um you
can get a two-hour video course. And I
also teach you how to create that video,
by the way, that you just watched. I
have that on uh on my I have that video
that I just showed you right here.
Oh, here's the guide, by the way. This
is the guide.
The link is in bio. It's not going to go
anywhere. So, don't rush out of here and
go get it now. It's not going to go
anywhere. Stick around.
Any questions?
I would love to leave. What does that
mean?
What does Lee mean? You misspelled
something. Oh, the app. Sorry if you're
asking me the app, Carly, if you're
still here. It's called Google Flow.
Dr. Cool, how you doing, man? How you
doing? I'm looking in my chat right now.
Ada, I just see some um I'm just going
to call out some names that I recognize,
okay? And if I missed it, I still
recognize your name, but I might have
missed it. Okay? We got a few people
that I know. Uh we got uh I don't know
how to say that name, but it's familiar
to me. LTO LTO Cappy.
Here guys, if you're watching this, um
let me take a breather here because I'm
tired, man.
I want to I'm going to show that smile.
You still here or no? He was here a long
time.
Smile's not here, but I'll send him that
video later. I made that Bigfoot video
that he asked for. Try to make it better
for him.
Thank you. 56,000 likes, man. You guys
are helping me out a lot by doing that.
And by you guys, I think 90% of it is
one person. Thank you. Appreciate
everybody that's doing that, too.
Where is my um
I'm going to get back to V2, V3, guys,
in a second. Don't leave yet.
I'm not done yet. I'm not done yet.
All right, let's see. Yep, I'm here. Oh,
okay. Cool. I didn't see your name on
the list. You might have hopped off or
and then maybe came back
>> cuz you were here for a long time and
your name was up on top.
>> Oh, no. Your name is here. Number three.
My bad. You're here.
So we got
>> we got DK skin gloss AI. We got DK again
number two. She has two accounts. Smile
Logan Alex trash Panda Lto Poppy Don Pio
Don Pio8 T.
And then number 10 is Shark Sheran the
Tiger.
I got to stand up.
>> Look at that. Look at this heart guys.
She's tapping. Let me see if you guys
can tap all together. Let me see if it
it multiplies. I see one stream.
>> Let me see if multiple people tap and
will create two streams.
>> You see my screen?
>> No, I don't think so. It's just one
stream. Okay.
>> All right. So, this um YouTube I'm going
to leave you guys. All right. So, I'm
going to stay on TikTok, but this is my
end of my YouTube live.
>> So, if you're on YouTube watching this,
I appreciate it. Or if you're watching
after it's being recorded,
>> I'll catch you guys next time.
Diamond.